Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of United States Politics and Government Serials TAM.759
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of United States Politics and Government Serials
1898-2013
1940-1989
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
National Alliance Publications, Inc.
The New Federalist
TAM.759
23.7 Linear Feet in 16 manuscript boxes, 2 half manuscript boxes, 9 custom enclosures, and 21 flat boxes
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of United States Politics and Government Serials contains over 300 titles on politics in the United States (US) and federal, state, and local governments in the US. The collection dates between 1898 and 2013, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1940s through 1980s.
Arrangement
Serials in this collection are arranged alphabetically by title.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to users without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection combines serials relating to United States politics and government drawn from two discrete groups of material held by the Tamiment Library. The first was a partially inventoried backlog of serials, received by the library through donations, subscriptions, and in archival collections. The second group consisted of around 1,700 serials, newspapers, and magazines, organized by title as an artificial collection, referred to as Periodicals.001 or Boxed Newspapers. This material was combined, inventoried, and arranged and described in subject-based categories in 2017. The accession number related to this collection is 2017.049.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Due to the fragile nature of certain original materials, researchers may be required to consult microfilm copies, preservation photocopies, or digital images of material in this collection.
Scope and Contents
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of United States Politics and Government Serials contains over 300 titles on politics in the United States (US) and on federal, state, and local governments in the US. The collection dates between 1898 and 2013, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1940s through 1980s. Topics include issues in the Democratic and Republican parties, libertarian politics, Puerto Rican independence movements, and elections at all levels of government. The collection includes newsletters published by members of the US Congress, members of the People's Party, discussion of presidential elections in the 1970s and 1980s, and issues of race in politics. Large runs of titles include The National Alliance, The New Federalist, and In Fact.
United States -- Politics and government -- Periodicals.; United States -- Politics and government -- Newspapers.; United States -- Politics and government -- 20th century.; Puerto Rico -- History -- Autonomy and independence movements; Political campaigns.; Political culture -- United States; Government accountability -- United States.; The new federalist
- 1986-NYS Voting Guide: National Organization for Women, New York, NY (Box 18, Folder 13)
- 1st of the Month: First of the Month Writers' Collective, New York, NY, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- 6 Months of Spotlight: A Review of Spotlight's Work and a Perspective for Summer Circulation: Claudia Jones / American Youth for Demcoracy, New York, NY, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- A Reply to President Johnson: Students for a Democratic Society, Cambridge, MA, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- ABC of Parliamentary Law: Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers, Bryn Mawr, PA, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Abolish Selective Service Flyer: Students for a Libertarian Society, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Action: Action, Inc., New York, NY, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Action Alert: Middle East Justice Network, Cambridge, MA, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- ADA Legislative Report: Americans for Democratic Action, New York, NY, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- ADA New York Monthly: Americans for Democratic Action, New York, NY, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ADA News: Americans for Democratic Action, New York, NY, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ADA Today: Americans for Democratic Action, Washington, DC, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 13, Box 44, Folder 1)
- ADA World: Americans for Democratic Action, Washington, DC, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4, Box 44, Folder 2)
- Action Update: Quixote Center, Hyattsville, MD, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Agenda: New Jewish Agenda, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Agitator: People's Organization for Progress (POP), Newark, NJ, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Al-Awda: New Jersey Solidarity-Activists for the Liberation of Palestine, New Brunswick, NJ, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- ALP State News: American Labor Party, New York, NY, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Alternative: Alternative, Naperville, IL, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Alternative Futures: The Journal of Utopian Studies: Human Dimensions Center, Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute and University of Michigan, Troy, NY, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Alternatives/80's Coalition for a People's Alternative Newsletter: Coalition for a People's Alternative, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Alternatives: A Forum for Activism in the Seventies: The Oberlin Political Caucus, Oberlin, OH, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- American Opinion: Belmont, MA, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- American Sociologist: American Sociological Association, Washington, DC, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- American Spectator: American Spectator, Inc., Dunellen, NJ, 1932-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- American Ultras: New America, New York, NY, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Americana: Americana Group, Inc., New York, NY, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Americas: The Council for Pan American Democracy, New York, NY, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Arise!: National Liberation Struggles Support Committee, New York, NY, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Arm the Spirit: National Committee to Free Puerto Rican Prisoners of War, Chicago, IL, 1990-1992; 1992 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- ARPA: Anthropologists for Radical Political Action Newsletter, Washington, DC, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Arrow: International Committee Against Racism Magazine, Brooklyn, NY, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Austin Duckweed: The Austin Duckweed, Austin, TX, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Bald Eagle: Bald Eagle, USA, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Banner: Coalition to Stop Gun Violence, Washington, DC, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 26, Box 44, Folder 3)
- Basic Documents: National Education Department of the Workers Party of the USA, New York, NY, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Big Apple Libertarian: New York City Chapter of the Libertarian Party, New York, NY, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Big Business Day: Big Business Day, Washington, DC, Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Big Idea: Big Idea, Massillon, OH, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Black Community Newsletter: Black Panther Party, Philadelphia, PA, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Blaze: Democracy Unlimited, St. Louis, MO, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- BNA Special Report: Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., Washington, DC, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 22)
- Bottom Line/Personal: Boardroom Reports, Inc., New York, NY, 1985-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
- Bowdwitch Review: Unitas, Berkeley, CA, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Bread and Roses: Bread & Roses School, Seattle, WA, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Bridge: Center for Research and Education, Denver, CO, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- The BSRL Newsletter: An Occasional Publication of the Bank for Socially Responsible Lending Organizing Group, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Bulletin: Interim Committee for a New Puerto Rican Solidarity Movement, Chicago, IL, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Bulletin: Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, Santa Barbara, CA, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Bulletin of the Greek American Council: Greek American Council, New York, NY, 1945-1947 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- By What Authority: Program on Corporations, Law & Democracy, South Yarmouth, MA, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Campaign Against US Intervention - Legislative Update: Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy, Washington, DC, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Campaigner Special Report: Campaigner Publications, Inc., New York, NY, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Campus ADA Bulletin: Americans for Democratic Action, New York, NY, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Capitalist Reporter: Capitalist Reporter Inc., New York, NY, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- CARF: Anti-Racist, Anti-Fascist Co-ordinating Committee (ARAFCC), USA, Undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Carta Semanal del Movimiento pro Independencia de Puerto Rico: Vanguardia de Puerto Rico, Rio Piedras, Puerto Rico, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Cause and Cure: Jacob S. Coxey, Massillon, OH, 1898 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- CCR Update: Center for Constitutional Rights, New York, NY, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Center Diary: Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, Santa Barbara, CA, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Centro de Estudios Puertorriquenos Bulletin: Centro de Estudios Puertorriquenos, New York, NY, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- CEP Newsletter: Council on Economic Priorities, New York, NY, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Challenge: Americans of Italian Descent, Inc., New York, NY, 1971 (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 1)
- Changes: PEER Collective, Simpsonville, MD, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Circle Anti-Imperialist Weekly: Anti-Imperialist Student Organization, Chicago, IL, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Citizen Action News: Citizens Action League, San Francisco, CA, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Citizen Advocate: Massachusetts Fair Share, Boston, MA, 1979-1983 (Box 14, Folder 8-9)
- Citizens Progressive: Texas Citizens Party, Austin, TX, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Citizens Voice: Citizens Party, Washington, DC, 1981-1983 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Citizens Voice: Citizens Party of Indiana, Indianapolis, IN, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 12, Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 2)
- Citizens Voice: Citizens Party of Northern California, Berkeley, CA, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Citizens Voice: Citizens Party, San Francisco Chapter, San Francisco, CA, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Claridad: Betances Publishers, Inc., New York, NY, 1972-1980 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
- Claridad: Claridad, San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1972-1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Clark for President News: Clark for President Committee, Washington, DC, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Claustrophobia: Claustrophobia, Baltimore, MD, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Closer up: Upton Close, Washington, DC, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Coalition for Economic Survival: Coalition for Economic Survival, Los Angeles, CA, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Comment: New Perspectives in Libertarian Thought: Comment, Burlington, VT, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Committee Against Fascism: CAF, Brooklyn, NY, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Common Cause/Maryland Watchdog: Common Cause/MD, Annapolis, MD, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Common Cause/MD: Common Cause/MD, Annapolis, MD, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Common Ground: New York Revolutionary Committee, New York, NY, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Common Home Messenger: The Common Home Messenger, Payson, IL, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Committee in Support of Solidarity Reports: Committee in Support of Solidarity, New York, NY, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Committee of Correspondence Newsletter: Committee of Correspondence, New York, NY, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Common Sense: Common Sense, Inc., New York, NY, 1933-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17, Box 3, Folder 8-10, Box 44, Folder 5-6)
- Common Sense: An Indpendent Student Journal: Common Sense, New York, NY, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Commonweal: Catholic Library Association, Haverford, PA, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Communique for New Politics: Community for New Politics, Berkeley, CA, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Community Economic Workshops: League for Economic Democracy, San Pedro, CA, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Community Voice: Lackawanna Discussion Group, USA, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Comparative Poliltical Studies: Sage Publications, Beverly Hills, CA, 1968-1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Con$cience & Military Tax Campaign: Con$cience & Military Tax Campaign, Bellport, NY, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Congress Watcher: Public Citizen's Congress Watch, Washington, DC, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Congressman Ted Weiss News: Washington, DC, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Congressman Ted Weiss Reports: 17th Congressional District Office, New York, NY, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Connections: North American Coordinating Committee for NGOs on the Question of Palestine, Washington, DC, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Constitution Party: Upton Close, Washington, DC, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Correo de la Quincena: Correo de la Quincena, Guaynabo, Puerto Rico, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Council on Economic Priorities Newsletter: Council on Economic Priorities, New York, NY, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Council Watch: New York Public Interest Research Group, Inc., New York, NY, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- CovertAction Bulletin: CovertAction, Washington, DC, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- CTJ Update: Citizens for Tax Justice, Washington, DC, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Current Economic Comment: University of Illinois College of Commerce and Business Administration, Champaign, IL, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- The Daily Spectacle: Spectacular Media, Lansing, MI, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- De pie y en lucha: Puerto Rican Commission of the Movimiento de Liberacion Nacional, Chicago, IL, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Debunker: Haldeman-Julius Company, Girard, KS, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Democratic Action: Campus Americans for Democratic Action, New York, NY, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Democratic Agenda: Democratic Agenda, New York, NY, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Democrats Today: Democratic National Committee, Washington, DC, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Demokratia: Demokratia, New York, NY, 1968-1975 (Box 31, Folder 15-22, Box 18, Folder 25, Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 3)
- Department for Professional Employees News: Department of Professional Employees, Washington, DC, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Development International: Development International, Inc., Arlington, VA, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Dialogue: International Communication Agency, Washington, DC, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Diario de la Marina: Diario de la Marina, Miami Beach, Fl, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Digest of Council Meeting: Greater New York Industrial Union Council, New York, NY, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Digest of World Wide Activities of Enemies of Freedom: Federation to Fight Fascism, Flushing, NY, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Direct Action: Livermore Action Group, Berkeley, CA, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- District 21 Report: Representative Niilo Koponen, Fairbanks, AK, 1980-1989 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Duck Book Digest: Robert White, Inc., Cocoa, FL, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Eat the State!: A Forum for Anti-authoritarian Political Opinion, Research, and Humor: Eat the State, Seattle, WA, 2004-2011 (Box 15, Folder 7-15)
- Economic Democrat: A Publication of the Campaign for Economic Democracy: California Campaign for Economic Democracy, Santa Monica, CA, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Eighty One Forty One: Technocracy, Inc., Akron, OH, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- El Coqui: LUCHA, New York, NY, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- El Diario De La Gente: University of Colorado, Boulder, CO, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- El Pueblo Luchador: El Pueblo Luchador, Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Election Bulletin: Committee for a Representative Convention Delegation, New York, NY, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Election Update: National Committee for an Effective Congress, Washington, DC, 1984-1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Equity Series: CF Taylor, Philadelphia, PA, 1910-1913 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- ERA Monitor: Equal Rights Amendment Project, Sacramento, CA, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Ergo: Ergo, Cambridge, MA, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Fact Sheet: The Committee to Defend V. J. Jerome, New York, NY, Undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Facts Forum News: Facts Forum News, Dallas, TX, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- FCNL Action: Friends Committee on National Legislation, Washington, DC, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Fight for Peace: American Youth for Democracy, New York, NY, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Fire Next Time: The Fire Next Time / SDS, Chicago, IL, Undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
- First AD Citizen: American Labor Party, New York, NY, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- First-Strike Papers: Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy, Washington, DC, Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- For Your Information: Americans for Democratic Action, Washington, DC, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Free Enterprise: We, The People, Phoenix, AZ, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Free Enterprise: We, The People, Chicago, IL, 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Free Puerto Rico!: Free Puerto Rico, Chicago, IL, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Free World: Cooperative League of the USA, Chicago, IL, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Freedom Monitor: Freedom House, New York, NY, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 14, Box 31, Folder 13)
- Freedom Writer Magazine: Institute for First Amendment Studies, Great Barrington, MA, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Friends of Ron Dellums Newsletter: Committee for Congressman Ronald V. Dellums, Washington, DC, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Frontlash Organizing News: Frontlash, Inc, Washington, DC, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Frontlash Organizing News: Frontlash, Inc, New York, NY, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Full Disclosure: Full Disclosure, Ann Arbor, MI, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- G: Green Party of New York State, Brooklyn, NY, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Genesis: Washington State Peace and Freedom Party, Seattle, WA, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Goob Yeak Gergibal: Goob Yeak Gergibal, East Lansing, MI, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Good Government: John L. Porter, Kansas City, KS, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Grass Roots: National Newsletter of the People's Party: People's Party, Washington, DC, 1972-1975 (Box 13, Folder 30, Box 16, Folder 9-15)
- Greek American: Greek American Publishing, Inc., Long Island City, NY, 1987-1998 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Greek-American Tribune: Proodos Publishing Co., Inc., New York, NY, 1941-1946 (Box 35, Box 36, Box 37, Box 38, Box 39, Box 40, Box 41, Box 42, Box 43)
- Haiti Alert!: Friends of Haitian Refugees, South Miami, FL, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Headlines: Headlines, New York, NY, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Henry George Newsletter: Henry George School of Social Science, New York, NY, 1981-1990 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Heretics: National Insider, Chicago, IL, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Hightower Lowdown: The Hightower Lowdown, New York, NY, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Human Events: Human Events, Inc., Washington, DC, 1957-1973 (Box 5, Folder 22, Box 17, Folder 2)
- Il Manifesto: Appalachian Movement Press, Huntington, WV, Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Immigration Law Bulletin: National Center for Immigrants' Rights, Los Angeles, CA, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- In Context: Context Institute, Bainbridge Island, WA, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- In Fact: In Fact, Inc., New York, NY, 1940-1950 (Box 5, Folder 25-26, Box 6, Folder 1-9, Box 7, Folder 1-6, Box 8, Folder 1-5, Box 32, Folder 14)
- Independent: Independent Citizens Committee for the Arts, Sciences and Professions, New York, NY, 1945-1946 (Box 17, Folder 3, Box 13, Folder 31)
- Independent Politics News: A Publication of the Independent Progressive Politics Network: Independent Progressive Politics Network, Brooklyn, NY, 1997-2003 (Box 17, Folder 4-6)
- indy kids!: IndyKids, New York, NY, 2013 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- INFACT Update: INFACT, Boston, MA, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Inside In These Times: Institute for Public Affairs, Chicago, IL, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Insights: Grassroots International, Somerville, MA, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Insurgent: Committee to Fight Repression, New York, NY, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 29-30, Box 31, Folder 10)
- Inter/change: National Conference for New Politics, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Intercontinental Press: Intercontinental Press, New York, NY, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- InterDependent: United Nations Association of the USA, New York, NY, 1993-1996 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- International Democrat: National Democratic Institute for International Affairs, Washington, DC, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Interpreter: M.J. Loomis and R. Borsodi, Brookville, OH, 1946-1951 (Box 4, Folder 15-18)
- Interpreter Releases: American Council for Nationalities Service, New York, NY, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 10-11)
- Iraqi Democratic Voice: Iraqi Democratic Union in USA and Canada, Ferndale, MI, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Issue Brief: Citizens' Congress on National Security, St. Louis, MO, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Jamaica: The Jamaica Progressive League, Inc., New York, NY, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Journey of Post Keynesian Economics: M.E. Sharpe, Inc., Armonk, NY, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- KADAMAY Quarterly: Filipino Workers Center, New York, NY, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- L'enrage: Comite d'Action, Berkeley, CA, Undated (Box 31, Folder 24)
- La Escalera: Publicaciones Geranisam, Rio Piedras, Puerto Rico, Undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
- La Federacion Obrera Puertorriquena: Federation of Puerto Rican Workers, Bronx, NY, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- La Federacion Obrera Puertorriquena: Young Lords Party, New York, NY, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- La Gente de Aztlán: UCLA Communications Board of the Associated Students, Los Angeles, CA, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- La Patria Radical: Movimiento de Liberacion Nacional Puertorriqueno, Chicago, IL, 1988-1993 (Box 17, Folder 8-13)
- Law & Disorder: Donald Myrus and Burton Joseph, Chicago, IL, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Legislative Bulletin: Legislative Council of the New York City Chapter of the National Lawyers Guild, New York, NY, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- LI Progressive: The Research and Education Project of Long Island, Massapequa, NY, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Liberal Democrat: Thomas Winnett, Berkeley, CA, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Liberal Digest: Liberal Party / Shulsinger Brothers, Inc., New York, NY, 1945-1965 (Box 9, Folder 2-6)
- Liberal Opinion: Liberal Opinion, Vinton, IA, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Liberal Review: Liberal Review Co., Chicago, IL, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Liberty Amendment: Liberty Amendment Committee of the U.S.A., Los Angeles, CA, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Liberty Bulletin: Citizens Committee for Constitutional Liberties, New York, NY, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Looking Ahead: National Planning Association, Washington, DC, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 7, Folder 9)
- LP News: Libertarian Party, Washington, DC, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- MAFNET Internal Bulletin: The Midwest Antifascist, Columbus, OH, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- MaryPIRG: Maryland Public Interest Research Group Citizen Lobby, Baltimore, MD, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Masks: Masks, Stanford, CA, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Ministry of Information Black Paper: Black Panther Party for Self-Defense, Oakland, CA, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 3, Box 18)
- Modern Thinker: The Modern Thinker, Inc., New York, NY, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Modern Thinker: Current Thinker, Inc., New York, NY, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Modern Thinker: Contemporary Literary Publications, Inc., New York, NY, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Monocle: Monocle Goe's Quarterly: Monocle Periodicals, Inc., New York, NY, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Monthly Bulletin: Constitution Revision Committee, Newark, NJ, 1951-1952 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Move Over: The Citizens Party Newsletter: Citizens Party, Madison, WI, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Movement & Party: The Peoples' Alliance, New York, NY, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Muckraker: Center for Investigative Reporting, San Francisco, CA, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Naptar: Naptar, New York, NY, 1951 (Box 32, Folder 1)